tuttlepublishing.com 2018-08-10

# Privacy Policy

Tuttle Publishing is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy in all aspects of our business. 

** ** **What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

·         When ordering, we need to know your full name, email address, shipping address, billing address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date in order to process and fulfill your order.

·         When you sign up for services like email newsletters, we only need an email address to send you the request information.

·         We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important functionality changes to our services, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, visit your account to change your preferences.

** ** **How do we protect your personal information?**

We use the latest encryption technology to keep your personal information safe.  All of your ordering information including your name, address, and credit/debit card number is encrypted using a secure server for maximum security. Your card and billing information cannot be read en route to our ordering system. To ensure that your information is even more secure, once we receive your credit card information it is stored in a secured, 128-bit encrypted, highly protected and separate environment.

Credit card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution, which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information purely to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions.

** ** **What are cookies and why are they useful?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our service uses cookies to speed navigation and keep track of items. We use cookies to remember information you gave to us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit us. Many improvements and updates to our service are based on the data derived from these cookies, such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies, but please note that this will create some loss of site functionality.

** ** **Will we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**

Tuttle does not disclose personally identifying information. We may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such a release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of our employees, our users, or others.

** ** **How do we allow you to update or change your personal information?**

Upon request, we will (a) correct personal information that you notify us is erroneous, or (b) permit you to 'opt out' of further e-mail contact while still allowing access to the site. To request a correction or cancellation, or to 'opt out' of further e-mail contact, please **contact** us by email at info [at] tuttlepublishing.com.

**Links**

Our site contains links to other sites, including content from other sites that is occasionally framed within our site. Please note that the privacy policies at these other sites may be different than our own. We remind you to review the privacy policy of any site linked to or framed within our site prior to providing any information.

**Consent**

By using our website and services, you consent to our collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
